509-768-0294

JonJazdzewski@gmail.com JonJazd.com

18111 25th Ave NE Marysville 98271

PROFILE

Though I have worked in healthcare for five years, engineering and technical skills have long been my passions. I built and troubleshot my own computer, and I enjoy the problem solving inherent to coding and software. At home, I help raise three children, enjoy reading, and love to cook.

EXPERIENCE

Clinical Laboratory Scientist, LabCorp; Seattle, WA — 2018–Present

Responsible for the testing and safekeeping of patient samples. Measure lab results while adhering to strict safety policies and HIPPA regulations. Troubleshoot each device in the lab and routinely interact with other hospital personnel to ensure continuity of information.

Site Manager, Echo League; Spokane, WA — 2016-2018

Helped develop the league's website and managed the back-end skill-conversion algorithm. Created and troubleshot a Discord bot to push ads at set intervals using specialized code to correct redundancy issues.

Clinical Laboratory Specialist, Rockwood Clinic; Spokane, WA — 2016-2018

Responsible for the manual and automatic testing of patient samples and worked with several proprietary software systems.

Lab Tech, Pathology Associates Medical Lab; Spokane, WA — 2015-2016

Tested patient samples, verified the results, and learned the various systems and devices for this career field.

EDUCATION

Oregon State University, Corvallis, OR — B.S. Computer Science, 2021 Shoreline Comm. Coll., Shoreline, WA — Med. Lab Tech Certification, 2014 Point Loma Nazarene University, San Diego, CA — B.S. Chemistry, 2012

Skills

Proficient with programming languages SQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, C, and C++. Samples can be found at JonJazd.com

Familiar with Office Suites, Bash/Terminal, and VScode. Experience with medical software from Siemens, Inova, Sysmex, Stago, and others.

REFERENCES

Alex Muench: Echo League, Lead Developer: ammuench@gmail.com

Sondra Powers: LabCorp, Medical Lab Technician: sondraLpowers@gmail.com

Lucas Rafferty: LabCorp Hematology Supervisor: rafferL@labcorp.com